

SHANMUGA PRIYA M

shanmugapriyashanu2002@gmail.com



+91 9080888421



7, Raj Nagar 3rd Street, Shanthi Nagar, Madurai-625018



https://github.com/Priya-shan











M Gmail

Profile

I am a B.E CSE Undergraduate, My passion towards this tech field has continuously driven me to expand my knowledge, experience skills. Throughout my life, l've approached every challenge with enthusiasm. creativity, ceaseless desire to expand my knowledge. This have paved the way to countless opportunities and unique experiences.

Skills

Java	• • • •
Python	• • • • •
С	• • • • •
Data Structures	• • • •
HTML5	• • • •
CSS3	• • • •
Java Script	• • • • •
Bootstrap	• • • •
Communication	• • • •
Leadership	• • • •

Professional Experience

Web Development Internship

The Sparks Foundation, Virtual July 2021 - Aug. 2021

Worked on several tasks related to Web Development and managed to complete the tasks within the deadline.

UI/UX Developer (Internship)

V7lancers, Madurai

Aug. 2021 - Sept 2021

Assisted Technical team in a real time project by designing UI and developing it into a website within the given deadline. Worked with a nice team, I mainly worked on frontend part. Had good communication with clients and redesigned UI as per their needs.

Web Developer (Internship)

Lets Grow More, Virtual Sept. 2021 - Oct. 2021

Developed given design into a website and also worked on tasks related to web development.

Campus Business Manager (Internship)

Prepbytes, Virtual;

June 2021 - Nov. 2021

Being the point of contact of Prepbytes in my college acquired leadership quality. Gained valuable skills in digital marketing and social media marketing via execution of marketing events, contests, and campaigns for the community. Also I have been awarded the star campus business manager of the week.

Academic Background

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science and Engineering

Velammal college of engineering and technlogy

Madurai, Tamil Nadu Expected to graduate in 2023 CGPA - 9.44 (upto sem 4)

Higher Secondary (XII)

C.E.O.A Matric higher secondary school Madurai, Tamil Nadu 2018 - 2019 Percentage - 87.83%

Secondary (X)

C.E.O.A Matric higher secondary school Madurai, Tamil Nadu 2016 - 2017 Percentage - 98.4%

Achievements

Won 1st Prize in Hack Salvation at Synsara'21

A National level Virtual Hackathon conducted by Sri Sai Ram Engineering college, Chennai.

Winner of Java Programming League

A Coding contest organized by CSE dept. at Velammal college of engineering & Technology, Madurai.

Won 1st Prize in Paplectio

A Paper presentation contest conducted by CSI State level student convention, TamilNadu

Volunteering

NSS Volunteer

Actively participated in social activities.

Open Source Contributor

Contributed to open source projects.

Programming Projects

Minds Eye 2.0

Super Interactive game in Java.

Created a gaming application especially made for ADHD children that would improve their remembrance level and attention span.

Care & Cure

Hospital Management System in Java.

A Java Application designed to replace manual paper based system used in hospitals to maintain patient information, Room availability, Patient invoices and so on with a timely retrieval of any information.

More Projects on Github !!!

Others

Attended a 2 days workshop on "Internet of Things (lot)" at National Institute of Technology, Trichy (NIT)

Participated in Toycathon-2021, A National level toy Hackathon organized by central government of India, and led my team to grand finale

Participated in Guinness World Record Event - Most users to take an online computer programming lesson in 24 hours.

Personal Details

D.O.B: 22/04/2002

Father's Name: Murugan S

Languages known: Tamil, English

Declaration

I hereby declare that all the information given above is true and correct to the best of my knowledge.

Station: Madurai Date: 09/11/2021

Signature : M.5